Edward Livingston Papers, 1683-1877 (bulk 1764-1836 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 13: John Cox, Jr. (1756-1825), surveyor and estate agent to Margaret Beekman Livingston, Janet Montgomery and others, 1762-1825; 1771-1825; 7 boxes
  - Subseries 13A: Correspondence, 1771-1825; 5 boxes
    - General Correspondence, 1772-1825; 3 boxes
      - General Correspondence, 1816; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence, 1818; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence, 1819; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - General Correspondence, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - General Correspondence, 1821; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - General Correspondence, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - General Correspondence, 1823; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - General Correspondence, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - General Correspondence, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - General Correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Folder 18)
    - Cox Family, 1771-1801; 1 box
      - John Cox, Jr. Family Correspondence, 1771-1799; portion of 1 box
        - Burnham, Elizabeth (Cox) (Sister), 1783; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Cox, Elizabeth, b. 1776 (Daughter), 1790-1792; 3 folders (Folder 2-4)
        - Cox, George (Brother), 1786-1792; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Cox, Jameson (Brother), 1783-1799; 16 folders (Folder 6-21)
        - Cox, John, Sr. (Father), 1771-1792; 14 folders (Folder 22-35)
        - Cox, Joseph (Brother), 1799; 1 folder (Folder 36)
        - Cox, Maritje, b. 1755 (Wife), 1790; 1 folder (Folder 37)
        - Cox, William (Brother), 1776-1786; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Correspondence of Other Family Members, 1774-1801; portion of 1 box
        Includes correspondence of Henry Brockholst Livingston, John Livingston, Peter R. Livingston, and Philip Livingston.
        - Cox, Maritje, b. 1755, 1785-1797; 1 folder (Folder 39)
        - Cox, John, Sr., 1774; 1 folder (Folder 40)
        - Livingston, Henry Brockhoist, 1759-1823 (Cousin, Princeton Class of 1774), 1778-1815; 1 folder (Folder 41)
        - Livingston, John (Uncle), 1756; 1 folder (Folder 42)
        - Livingston, Peter R. (Ancestor) (Princeton Class of 1758), 1779; 1 folder (Folder 43)
        - Livingston, Philip, 1716-1778 (Uncle), circa 1770; 1 folder (Folder 44)
  - Subseries 13B: Financial Records, 1773-1823; 1 box
    Includes accounts, receipts, bills of sale, and some notebooks.
    - Accounts, Receipts, and Bills of Sale, Etc., 1773-1823; 1 folder (Folder 1-2)
    - Items Found in the Ledger Of, 1784-1801; circa 1784-1801; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Accounts for Apples Sent to New York, 1792-1793; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Small Notebooks, undated; 1 folder (Folder 5)
  - Subseries 13C: Ledgers, 1762; 1770-1786; 1 box
    Contains one ledger used for accounts and various other purposes, and another ledger of curious origin.
    - Ledger, 1762; 1770-1786; portion of 1 box
      Also contains John Cox Jr. Family Records. Not sure about the real nature of this book.
    - John Cox Jr. Ledger, 1784-1801; portion of 1 box
  - Subseries 13D: Miscellaneous Papers, 1771-1797; 1 box
    Contains a wide variety of items, including ballads, items relating to a (Revolutionary War) regiment, legal papers, employment agreements, a deed, inventories, and a 1784 map of North America. See container list for details. See also the surveys of Clinton Township and Rensselaerwyck in the Series 17: Landholdings.
    - Ballads, Snatches and Bits of Prose, circa 1771-1778; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Advertisements, 1771-1792; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Memoranda, 1773-1790; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Personal Legal Matters, 1776-1790; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Items Relating to Snyder's Regiment, 1778-1779; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Employment Agreements, 1778-1790; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Deed for Property in the Hardenburgh Patent, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Inventories, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Printed Map of North America by John Hamilton More, London, 1784; 1 box
- Series 14: Benjamin French (fl. 1768-1777), Albany Area Merchant, 1755-1803; 1769-1803; 8 boxes
  French was an Albany area merchant whose estate was forfeited to the State of New York. According to a note by Alexander Hamilton to (Charles McEvers), undated, French was charged with an offense under the confiscation law (of New York) on October 31, 1777, but the judgement was not signed until 1783. His papers were eventually forwarded to Gulian Verplanck, D.C. Verplanck, and William Laight for the use of creditors. Edward Livingston was engaged by the three to attempt to collect monies due French's estate, and eventually purchased a portion of the rights to it. (See letter of Edward Livingston to Charles Taylor, 3/2/1793 in Correspondence) It is also evident from this same letter that French died sometime before 1784. I have not been able to locate French in any of the current indexes of Loyalist records, perhaps because he died before he could file a claim for lost property with the British government. French's name does appear, however, on a list of persons suspected of loyalism garnered from the records of the Commissioners of Conspiracy (of New York), and on two lists of confiscated and forfeited estates compiled from documents of the Commissioners of Sequestration and the Commissioners of Forfeitures (also of New York). (See New York in the Revolution as a Colony and State, Supplement, Albany, New York: Oliver A. Quayle, 1901.) French's brothers Charity and Gershom also appear on these lists. Records of Charity French's claim can be found in Peter Wilson Coldham's American Loyalist Claims, Washington, D.C.: National Genealogical Society, 1980 and Gregory Palmer's Biographical Sketches of Loyalists of the American Revolution, Westport, (CT): Meckler Publishing, 1984. The latter work is a revised edition of Lorenzo Sabine's 19th century work under the same title.
  This series is arranged into three subseries: Papers Relating to Claims Concerning his Estate, Business Papers, and Ledger.
  - Subseries 14A: Papers Relating to Claims Concerning his Estate, 1768-1803; 1 box
    Contains correspondence, legal papers, accounts, including lists and schedules of debtors, notes and bonds, and miscellaneous papers relating to the legal actions that were pursued to try to collect old debts due to French's estate. The correspondents include Edward Livingston, Charles McEvers, David Alexander Grant, Curtis Hurd, John Ackley, and others. See also correspondents George William Erving and David Alexander Grant in Edward Livingston's Correspondence: General (Subseries 1A).
    - Correspondence, 1784-1801; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Legal Papers, 1777-1803; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Accounts, circa 1769-1800; portion of 1 box
      - Lists and schedules of debtors, circa 1770-1800; 2 folders (Folder 3-4)
      - Other, 1769-1794; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Notes and Bonds, 1768-1777; portion of 1 box
      - Numbered, as Pertaining to Lists and Schedules, 1769-1777; 2 folders (Folder 6-7)
      - Received from Le Roy Morris, 1768-1775; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Other, 1768-1775; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1777; 1 folder (Folder 10)
  - Subseries 14B: Business Papers, 1755-1793; 1768-1777; 6 boxes
    Consists of deeds, leases, accounts, and business papers of Benjamin French.
    - General File, 1755-1793; 1768-1777; 5 boxes
      These files include correspondence, bonds, receipts, accounts, orders for goods, promissory notes, warrants, summonses, etc. Other recipients of correspondence (besides Benjamin French) include Charity French, Gershom French, Moses Holt, and William Marsh.
      Arranged alphabetically by surname of correspondent, customer, etc., interspersed with general folders for some letters.
      - Abbot, John, 1770-1775; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Abeel and Byvanck, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Adams, Ephraim, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Adams, John, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        This John Adams joined Burgoyne's troops at Bennington in 1777.
      - Adams, Samuel, 1755-1774; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        This Samuel Adams came from Arlington, NY, near Poughkeepsie.
      - Addams, Elijah, 1771-1775; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Akin, Abraham and Edward, 1772-1774; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Alger, Asa, 1769-1770; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Allen, John, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Allen, Samuel (Captain), 1769-1774; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Allen, Seth, 1771-1774; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Andrews, Thomas, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Anthony, Zephania, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Arabic Packet (Sloop), 1774; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Arnold, Benedict, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Bancker, Evert, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Bancker, Flores, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Banyar, P., 1774; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Barber, John, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Barber, William, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Barber and Marvin, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Bay, John, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Beijfe?, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Bell, Samuel, circa 1775; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Benson, Egbert, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Best, Harme, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Betts, Ephraim, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Bidwell, David, 1769-1771; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Bishop, Lemuel, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Bleeker, John J., 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Bleeker, John N., 1776; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Bleeker, Rutger, 1772-1776; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Bloodgood, James, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Blowers, Alexander, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Bogart, Henry, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Boggs, James, 1771-1776; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Brooks, John, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Buells, Nathaniel, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Bullen, Charley, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Burnham, John Jr., 1770-1773; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - B-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Cambell, Daniel, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Cannon, John and LeGrand, 1774-1776; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Carman, J., 1770; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Carr, William, 1773-1774; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Case, Charles, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 46)
        Includes provisions for Continental Army at Fort George
      - Castle, David, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Clark, Jeremiah, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Clement, Jeremiah, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Cockburn, William, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Cole, Ebenezer, Freegift and Hugh, 1771-1775; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Collins, Pitman (Captain), 1772; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Conkey, Joshua, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Conklin, Joseph, 1776; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Conroy, William, 1772-1776; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Corbin, John, 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Covell, Simon, 1771-1776; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Cowen, James, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Crossfield and Totten, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Cross, Ichabod, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Crukshank, Alexander, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Curtenius, Peter and Sharpe, 1772-1774; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Curtis, Eleazer (Captain), 1775; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Cuyler, Abraham, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Cuyler, Harmanus (and Wendell), 1770-1776; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Cuyler, Jacob, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - c-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Daggett, Brotherton, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Dawson, Volkert, 1771-1772; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - DeGarmo, Jacob, 1771-1772; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - DeLancey, Stephen, 1771-1776; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Diamond, Thomas, 1770-1772; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Dickinson, Charles, 1775-1776; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Dickinson, Daniel, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Doty, Joseph, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Douw, Volkert P., 1772-1774; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Dox, Peter, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Duane, James, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Duer, William, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - D-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Earl, Nehemiah, 1771-1775; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Edwards, William, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Elmore, Samuel, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Elting, Peter/Elting, Varick and Co., 1775; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - E-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Fairchild, Jesse, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Fay, Jonas, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Fay, Joseph, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Fay, Stephen, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Fitch, William, 1771-1772; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Follet, John, 1774-1776; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Folsom, Samuel, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Fortune (Sloop), 1774; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Fowler, John, undated; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - French, Charity (Brother), 1771-1776; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - French, Gershom (Brother), 1772-1775; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - French, Jeremiah (Father), 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - French, Thomas, 1770-1773; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - F-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Galusha, David, 1772-1775; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Galusha, Jacob, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Gan, John A., 1775; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Gansvoort, Leonard, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Gardner, Benjamin, 1769-1770; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Gardnier, George, 1770-1771; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Garrison, Benjamin, 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Giddeon?, Giddings?, Joseph, undated; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Glen, Cornelius, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Glen, Henry, 1769; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Goodrich, Benjamin, 1772-1774; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Graham, Ennis, 1773-1774; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Gray, Elizabeth and James, 1772-1774; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Green, James, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Griffith, John, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - Griffith, Stephen, circa 1774; 1 folder (Folder 61)
      - Grousebeek, Harmon, 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 62)
      - Grousebeek, John, 1772-1774; 1 folder (Folder 63)
      - Haight, William, 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Hall, Thomas, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Harmon, Reuben, 1772-1775; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Harris, Richard, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Harris, Thaddeus, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Hawley Family, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        Includes correspondence with Andrew, Giden, James, Jehiel, Jephtha, Joshia, Nathan and Peter Hawley.
      - Haynes, David, 1772-1775; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Herrinton, Nathan, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Hokesby, Robert, 1772-1775; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Holmes, Nathaniel, 1775-1776; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Holmes, Zephaniah, 1774-1776; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Holt, Benjamin, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Holt, Moses (Captain), 1773-1776; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Hunt, John, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Hunter, John, 1771-1772; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - H-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Irish, Anne, undated; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Irish, David, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Irish, John, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - J-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Kip, Henry, James and Jonathan, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Knickerbacker, John Jr., 1772-1775; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - K-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - LaGrange, Arie, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Laight, Edward and William, 1769-1774; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Lansing, Jacob J., 1775; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Lansing, John Jr., 1775; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Lansingh, Abraham Jacob, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Lansingh, Garret G., 1773; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Lansingh, H., 1771; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Lansingh, Jeremiah, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Lansingh, John, 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Lansingh, Nicholas, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Lansingh, Philip, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Lansingh and Dox, 1771-1774; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Lawrence, Gideon, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Lawrence, John and Effingham, 1769-1771; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Leake, Robert, 1771-1775; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Leonard, Ebenezer, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Livingston, Abraham, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Livingston, Margaret Beekman?, 1773-1776; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Livingston, Philip, 1770-1775; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Livingston, Walter, 1776; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Long, John, 1773-1774; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Lott, Leonard, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Ludlow, James, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Lupton, William, 1769; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Malcolm, William, 1772-1774; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Man, Isaac, 1771-1774; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Marsh, Jacob, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Marsh, Sarah, undated; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Marsh, William, 1770-1775; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Marshalk, John, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Marvin, Ebenezer, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - McCrea, Stephen, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - McDavitt, Charles, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - McEvers, Charles, 1773-1776; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - McKey, John, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - McLean, John, 1774-1776; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - McNeil, Arch, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - McNiff, Patrick, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Merchant, Lewis and John, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Merselis, Henry, 1771-1772; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Millington, John, 1769-1772; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Mills, James, 1771-1772; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Morhouse, John, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Munger, Increase and Philip, 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Munro, Hugh, 1770-1771; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Munro, John, 1770-1774; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Murray, John and Robert, 1770-1773; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Myers, Manuel, 1769-1773; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - M-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Neer, Zachariah, 1770; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Nichols, William, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Noble, David, 1772-1775; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Norris, Joseph, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Nutting, Jothan, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - O'Hara, Henry, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Osborn, Shadrach, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Overocker, Mikel, 1774-1776; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - O-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Parsons, David, 1769-1770; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Patoen, John, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Perry, James, 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Phelps, Elisha, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Price, John, 1773-1774; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - P-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Quackenboss, Henry, 1771-1776; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Ray, Joseph, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Ray, Robert, 1772-1776; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Richey, Hugh, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Robinson, Samuel, 1770-1775; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Robson, Saul, 1770-1773; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Rogers, William, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Romans, Mary and Robert, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Roosevelt, John J., 1773; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Rose, Josiah, 1771-1775; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Row, Joseph, 1773-1774; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Russel, Samuel, 1772-1774; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - R-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Schiffington, John, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Schuyler, John Jr., 1771-1772; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Schuyler, Peter, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Seagrove, J., 1775; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Searl, Gideon, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Selfridge, William, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Shoemaker, Anthony, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Silvester, P., 1775; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Simonds, Benjamin, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Skene, Andrew, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Skene, Philip, 1771; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Slarrow, David, 1771-1776; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Sloan, John, 1773-1774; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Slocum, Peleg, 1768; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Snedeker, Richard, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Spicer, Benjamin, 1771-1775; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - Squire's Company, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 61)
      - Staats, Henry, 1769; 1 folder (Folder 62)
      - Stewart, Arch, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Stewart, James and Alex, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Stewart, Lemuel, 1771-1775; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Stoddard, Eliakim, 1774-1776; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Stoutenburgh, Peter, 1773-1775; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - S-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Ten Eyck, Henry, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Tillman, Christopher, 1774-1776; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Todd, Samuel, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Toneray, Daniel (Sgt.), 1776; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Trotter, John Jr., 1773; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Turner, Ichabod, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - T-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Underhill, Benjamin, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - United Colonies, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Van Alen, Barent, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Van Buren, Leonard, 1774-1776; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Van der Worken, 1772; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Van Rensselaer, John, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Van Schaick, Anthony, 1770-1775; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Van Schaick, John, 1773-1774; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Van Schaick, Mary, 1774-1775; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Van Schaick, Wessel, 1773-1774; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Van Vechten, Derick, 1772-1773; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Van Vechten, Lucas, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Van Vechten, Teunis, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Van Vleck, Abraham H., 1770-1775; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Van Vleck, Abraham K., 1775; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Van Vleck, Henry, 1769-1777; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Van Vleck and Kip, 1770-1776; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Visscher, Bastiaen and Matthew, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Vlack, Abraham, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - V-General, undated; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Wallace, Hugh and Alexander, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Ward, Aaron, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Waters, Samuel, 1769-1770; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Watkins, David, 1771-1772; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Watson, John, 1775; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Weber, Frederick, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Welles, Eliakim, 1769-1775; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Wells, Edmund, 1772-1775; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Wendel, Abraham, 1771-1775; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Wendell, Harmanus, 1773; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Wendell, Henry, 1769-1773; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Wendell, Jacob H., 1774; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Wendell, Jonathan H., 1775; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Whaler, Jacob, 1774; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Wheat, Jonathan, 1769-1770; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - White, Henry, 1770-1771; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Willcox, Hazard, 1771-1773; 1 folder (Folder 50)